Guide to the Director of Athletics Records, 1939-2007, bulk 1968-2007 UA.13.01.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Director of Athletics records
1939-2007, bulk 1968-2007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Athletics Dept. Vice President and Director of Athletics
UA.13.01.0002
26 Linear Feet
The Athletic Director plans, administers, and directs intercollegiate athletic activities at Duke University including staff, publicity, promotion, ticket sales, and assures the University's adherence to appropriate rules, regulations, and guidelines. Collection contains records relating to the operations and activities of the Duke University Athletic Director, 1939-2007, bulk 1968-2007. A majority of the material was accumulated during Tom Butters' tenure as Athletic Director. Materials present include general correspondence, seven subject files arranged by accession, and contracts and schedules. Major subjects include National Collegiate Athletic Association, Atlantic Coast Conference, Duke University team sports, scholarships, fundraising, Iron Dukes, Athletic Council, and facilities and grounds.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been in existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Portions of these materials are restricted by donor request.
Provenance
The Director of Athletics records were received by the University Archives as a transfer between 1982-2019.
Biographical and Historical Note
The Athletic Director plans, administers, and directs intercollegiate athletic activities at Duke University and interprets and participates in formulating extramural athletic policies. The Director employs and discharges coaching staff and other department employees on own initiative or at direction of board in charge of athletics. Additionally, the Director prepares and disseminates publicity to promote athletic events; plans and coordinates activities of coaching staff; prepares budget and authorizes department expenditures; plans and schedules sports events; and oversees ticket sales and income generated by ticket sales. The Athletic Director also works closely with coaches, staff, and University administration to ensure adhesion to University codes of conduct and rules and regulations set forth by the National Collegiate Athletic Association and the Atlantic Coast Conference.
Tom Butters was a graduate of Ohio Wesleyan University and former pitcher for Major League Baseball's Pittsburgh Pirates organization (1962-1964). Butters began his career at Duke in 1967 when he became Director of Special Events. He became Duke University's head baseball coach in 1968, a position he held until 1970. He later became director of the Iron Dukes (1970), Assistant Director of Athletics (1972-1975), and Associate Athletic Director and assistant to the chancellor in 1976. In 1977, Butters became Duke University's fifth Athletic Director, preceded by James DeHart (1926-1930), Wallace Wade (1931-1942, 1946), Eddie Cameron (1942-1972), and Carl James (1972-1976). As Athletic Director Butters was known as an intrepid fundraiser and is credited with upgrading several athletic facilities erected in the 1930s and 1940s. While serving on the National Collegiate Athletic Association's Basketball Committee, Butters was instrumental in negotiating a one billion dollar contract with CBS. Upon his retirement in 1998, Butters had spent thirty years of his professional career involved with Duke University Athletics. He was succeeded by Joe Alleva (1998-2008).
Collection Overview
Contains material pertaining to the daily activities of the Duke University Athletic Director. The collection is divided into nine series: general correspondence, contracts and schedules, and subject series arranged in accession order. A majority of the material was accumulated by Tom Butters as Assistant Director of Athletics (1972-1975), Associate Athletic Director (1976), and Athletic Director (1977-1998). However, a small amount of material was created by Butters' predecessors, Carl James (1972-1976) and Eddie Cameron (1942-1972).
General correspondence is divided into two subseries: alphabetical and chronological. Alphabetical correspondence documents communication with other university offices, faculty, staff, alumni, and students; colleagues at other educational institutions and professional organizations; and various fundraising and promotional campaigns and events. Chronological correspondence contains primarily outgoing correspondence concerning similar topics.
Subject files contain material relating to Butters' work with the University and various regional and national athletics organizations. Prominent subjects throughout include the National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) and the Atlantic Coast Conference (ACC). NCAA material includes correspondence, memoranda, and minutes concerning rules and regulations; annual conventions and special meetings; various committees including Division I Basketball Committee and Television Committee; and printed material. ACC material includes correspondence, memoranda, and minutes concerning annual meetings, workshops, and clinics; news and press releases; tournaments and bowl games; legislative proposals; and several committees including Television Committee and Restructuring Committee. Also present are materials relating to Butters' fundraising activities; work with the Iron Dukes and Alumni Association; Duke University Sports Hall of Fame nominees, inductees, and speeches; Athletics Council minutes and memoranda; and athletic facilities maintenance and upgrade projects including several made to Wallace Wade Stadium and Cameron Indoor Stadium.
Other material relating directly to Duke University athletics are sports files and scholarship athletes. Sports files contain rosters, stats, and contest reports for numerous men's and women's revenue and non-revenue sports. Scholarship material contains letters of intent, and correspondence concerning scholarship renewal and terms and conditions of acceptance. Additional noteworthy subjects include Title IX, College Football Association (CFA), Raycom, North Carolina Amateur Sports, National Association of College Athletic Directors (NACAD), and National Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women (NAIAW).
The Contracts and Schedules series contains contracts and agreements between Duke University and other colleges, universities, and academies, travel itineraries for road contests, game schedules, and lists of lettering athletes for several revenue and nonrevenue sports.
An addition (Accession UA2019-0087) contains correspondence and subject files, mostly dated 1996 to 2007.
Separated Material
One 8x10 black and white photograph of the 1965 varsity football team was removed from accession UA83-107. Also, seven floorplans of the Finch-Yeager Building created by Worth Younts Contract Interiors (1980-1981) were removed from accession UA84-58.
Related Material
Athletics Council records, 1908-1993
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Athletics Reference collection, 1888-2005
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Edmund M. Cameron Records, 1929 - 1972
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sports Information Office records, 1932-1973
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Trinity College (Durham, N.C.) Athletic Association Records, 1912-1937
University Archives/David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sex discrimination in sports -- United States; College sports -- United States -- Management; College sports -- Economic aspects -- United States; College athletes; Duke University. Athletics Dept. Vice President and Director of Athletics; Duke University. Cameron Indoor Stadium; Duke University. Dept. of Athletics; Duke University. Wallace Wade Stadium; National Collegiate Athletic Association; Duke University. Athletic Council; Duke University -- Football; Duke University -- Basketball; Duke University -- Athletics; Atlantic Coast Conference
- General Correspondence, 1968-1994, 3.5 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Contains correspondence documenting the daily activities of the Athletic Director and includes communication with other university offices; faculty, staff, alumni, and students; colleagues at other educational institutions and professional organizations; promotional campaigns; and various social and fundraising events. Correspondence is divided into two subseries: alphabetical and chronological. Chronological correspondence contains primarily outgoing correspondence.
  - Alphabetical Corresponcence, 1968-1980
    - A, 1970-1978 (Box 1)
    - B, 1971-1980 June, 5 folders (Box 1)
    - C, 1968-1980 July, 4 folders (Box 1)
    - D, 1970 Dec.-1980 May, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - E, 1971 July-1978 May (Box 1)
    - F, 1972 Sept.-1980 March, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - G, 1971 July-1980 June, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - H, 1971 Feb.-1976, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - H, 1977-1980 July (Box 2)
    - I, 1972-1980 Feb. (Box 2)
    - J, 1973, 1975-1979 (Box 2)
    - K, 1971 May-1980 June, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - L, 1972 March-1980 July, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - M, 1973 Feb.-1980 July, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Mc, 1969, 1971-1979, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - McGee, Mike, 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - N, 1971-1980 (Box 2)
    - O, 1971 Oct.-1980 May (Box 2)
    - P, 1970 Nov.-1980 July, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Q, 1979 (Box 2)
    - R, 1971 Oct.-1980 June, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Ross, J. David, 1971 May-1979 Jan. (Box 2)
    - S, 1971 Feb.-1980 May, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - T, 1970 June-1980 June (Box 3)
    - U, V, 1970-1980 June (Box 3)
    - W, 1970 Nov.-1980 July, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - X, Y, Z, 1971 Sept.-1980 Aug. (Box 3)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1980-1994
    - 1980, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - 1981, 4 folders (Box 3)
    - 1982, 4 folders (Box 3)
    - 1983, Jan.-April (Box 3)
    - 1983, May-Dec., 2 folders (Box 4)
    - 1984, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - 1985, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - 1986, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - 1987, Jan.-April, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - 1987 Dec.-1988 July (Box 4)
    - 1988 Aug.-1989 May (Box 4)
    - 1989 June-1990 Aug. (Box 4)
    - 1990 Sept.-1994 April (Box 4)
- Subject Files (UA82-116), 1953-1976, 2 boxes
  Accession contains bulletins, minutes, statistics, and correspondence pertaining to the Atlantic Coast Conference; contracts and schedules for non-revenue sports; and policies, minutes, and general information concerning Title IX. Additional subjects include NCAA and North Carolina Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women (NCAIAW).
  - Atlantic Coast Conference (ACC)
    - 1953-1965, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - ACC-bulletins, stats, audits, 1960-1966, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - ACC minutes, 1963-1971 Oct., 4 folders (Box 5)
    - ACC, 1972 Sept.-1980, 12 folders (Box 5)
  - Minor Sports (Baseball-Golf)-contracts, schedules, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Minor Sports (Lacrosse-Wrestling)-contracts, schedules, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) and ACC Regulations-letters & Memoranda, 1974-1979, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - North Carolina Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women (NCAIAW)- handbook and miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Title IX (Box 6)
    - Evaluation of current policies effecting, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Minutes, findings, and recommendations, 1974-1976 (Box 6)
    - State and national information, 1972-1976, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Committee information and collective data, 1975-1976 (Box 6)
- Subject Files (UA83-107), 1963-1980, 2.5 boxes
  Accession contains memoranda and correspondence with university administrators and faculty; council and committee reports and minutes; as well as newspaper clippings and printed material. Prominent subjects include Athletic Council, ACC, NCAA, Iron Dukes, and women's sports.
  - A.Kenneth Pye, 1972, 1976-1980, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Advertising Letters, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Associate Athletic Director applicant, 1980 Jan.-Feb. (Box 6)
  - Athletic Council, 1963-1980, 17 folders (Box 6)
  - Athletic Financing, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - ACC
    - 1963-1967, 5 folders (Box 6)
    - 1967-1971, 4 folders (Box 7)
    - ACC 1.6 Material, 1965-1967 (Box 7)
    - Operation Basketball, 1975 Nov. (Box 7)
    - Press and news releases, 1963-1971, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Award Winners, 1968-1972 (Box 7)
  - Award List, 1967-1969, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Baseball Committee, 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Baseball scheduling, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Bill Foster, 1978-1980 (Box 7)
  - Board Meeting, 1979 Feb., 1979 May, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Boy Scouts of America (BSA), 1977-1979 (Box 7)
  - BSA, Occoneechee Chapter (Raleigh) Report, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Chairman ACC, Athletic Director, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Coaches Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence and newspapers (Miscellaneous Bad), 1969-1980 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence and newspapers (Miscellaneous Good), 1966-1980, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Departmental meeting, 1975 October (Box 7)
  - Exhibition game, Russia-U.S.A. Volleyball, 1975 March-May (Box 7)
  - Fan Appreciation Day, 1978 (Box 7)
  - General Athletic Information, 1975-1977 (Box 7)
  - Hall of Fame, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
  - Home Insurance Agency, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Iron Duke Classic, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
  - Jim Friedrich (Dept. of Health, Phys. Ed., and Recreation), 1976-1980 (Box 7)
  - Lacrosse, Fencing, and Tennis, 1975-1976 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Dr. Robert Rankin, undated (Box 7)
  - Letters on Football scholarship request, 1975-1976 (Box 7)
  - Lion's Club, Raleigh-"A Brief History," 1963 (Box 8)
  - Meeting-men and women, 1975 Sept. (Box 8)
  - Mike Grosso, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - NCAA, 1964-1969, 6 folders (Box 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1972-1976 (Box 8)
  - Non-revenue Sports, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
  - Paul Detomo (Business Director), 1975-1980 (Box 8)
  - Policy, 1975-1979 (Box 8)
  - President Sanford, Terry, 1970-1980 (Box 8)
  - Promotion meeting, 1977-1979 (Box 8)
  - Robert E. Lee Prize, 1965-1976 (Box 8)
  - Scoreboard, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Staff meeting, notes, 1975 Feb. (Box 8)
  - Staff meeting, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Summer School, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Supervisor of Tutoring for Athletes-functions, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Travel roster, 1975 Sept.-Nov. (Box 8)
  - United States Track Coaches Association, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Women's Sports Liaison Committee, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Women's Sports Summary, 1977-1980 (Box 8)
  - YMCA (Durham), 1977-1979 (Box 8)
- Subject Files (UA84-58), 1975-1983, 4.5 boxes
  Accession contains correspondence and memoranda, council minutes and reports, surveys, various committee records, men's and women's athletic scholarship information; and football bulletins, correspondence, and schedules. Also present are sports files that contain rosters, stats, and contest reports. Additional subjects include athletic facilities, promotions, radio and television, and ACC and NCAA.
  - Alumni Admissions Advisory Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
  - Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women (AIAW), Steve Vacendek, 1980- 1982 (Box 9)
  - Athletic Council, 1981 (Box 9)
  - ACC
    - Bulletin, 1981 Jan. (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - General, 1978-1980 (Box 9)
    - ACC meeting, 1979 July (Box 9)
    - ACC meeting, 1980 May (Box 9)
    - ACC meeting, 1981 May (Box 9)
    - ACC meeting, 1982 April-May (Box 9)
    - Steve Vacendek, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
    - ACC workshop, 1981 July-Aug. (Box 9)
  - Basketball correspondence, 1980 Aug.-1981 Aug. (Box 9)
  - Basketball Bulletin, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
  - Budget information, 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Budget meetings, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Building (Wallace Wade), Andy Wallace, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
  - Butters, NCAA correspondence, 1980 July-1981 July (Box 9)
  - Butters, personal file, 1980 July-1981 July, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Cameron Indoor Stadium (Steve Vacendek), 1980 (Box 9)
  - A. Kenneth Pye, 1978-1981, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Children's Classic, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
  - Chuck Ramsey, South Swim, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Coke, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
  - Contributions, Wallace Wade Stadium, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Charles Huestis, 1979-1981 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence to Coaches, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence with Jack Adcock, 1977-1981 (Box 9)
  - Daniel F. Tulley Associates, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
  - Development Office, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Duke Sports, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Preventative Approach to Cardiovascular Disease (DUPAC), 1981 (Box 10)
  - Duke University Athletic Association staff, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - EEO, 1981 (Box 10)
  - Employees and staff
    - Buehler, Al, 1977-1982 (Box 10)
    - Brown, Larry, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
    - D'Armi, Tom, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
    - Krzyzewski, Mike, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
    - Woodyard, Lorraine, 1978-1981 (Box 10)
    - all others, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - Equipment room, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - Facility, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - Finch-Yeager Building, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - Football
    - 1981-1982 (Box 10)
    - Football Bulletins, 1980-1981, 1981 season, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Comments on Duke/East Carolina game, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Contracts, 1980-1982, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1980 Aug.-1981 Aug. (Box 10)
    - Football Schedule, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - General correspondence, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Hall of Fame, 1975, 1981 (Box 10)
  - Housing, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - Insurance, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - Iron Duke/Alumni Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 10)
  - Jeff Simons Sports Company, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - Jerry Miles, NCAA, 1978 Sept. (Box 10)
  - Jim's ACC Meeting, 1981, Feb., May, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Jim's ACC Television Meeting, 1981 June (Box 10)
  - Jim's ACC Workshop, 1981 Aug. (Box 10)
  - Dawn London/Millard Freeman, NCAA Volunteer for Youth, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Letters of recommendation, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - Tara McCarthy, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Mike Meads, 1978 Oct. (Box 10)
  - Memoranda, 1978-1981, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Metrosports, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
  - Metrosports/ACC, Outing at "The Greenbrier," 1981 July (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978-1982, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - NCAA (Box 11)
    - 1980 April-1981 Aug. (Box 11)
    - Eligibility form for NCAA Championships, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
    - Handbooks, 1981, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Institutional information and Sports Sponsorship form, 1979 (Box 11)
    - News, 1980 July-1981 Dec. (Box 11)
    - Office, Kansas, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
    - Signatures of coaches, 1978 Sept. (Box 11)
  - Other University personnel, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Edward Phillips, Pembroke Reality and Insurance, 1978 Aug.-Sept. (Box 11)
  - Ella Pratt, Cultural Affairs, 1978 June-July (Box 11)
  - Promotions, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Radio, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Racquet Ball, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Raycom, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Resumes, 1981, 1983, 4 folders (Box 11)
  - Terry Sanford, 1978, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
  - Scholarships
    - Baseball, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Basketball, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Football, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Golf, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Lacrosse, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Soccer, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Swimming,, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Tennis, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Track, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Women's Sports, 1976-1978 (Box 11)
    - Wrestling, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 11)
    - Termination Letters, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Shrine Club, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Sports
    - Baseball, 1975-1979, 4 folders (Box 11)
    - Baseball, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - Basketball, 1975-1979, 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Basketball-Women, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - Club Sports, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - Cross-Country, 1975-1979, 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Fencing, 1975-1981, 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Field Hockey, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - Football, 1975-1979, 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Golf, 1975-1979, 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Golf-Men and Women, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Gymnastics, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - Lacrosse, 1975-1981, 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Soccer, 1975-1981, 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Swimming, 1975-1981, 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Tennis, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
    - Tennis, 1976-1979, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Tennis-Men and Women, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Indoor/Outdoor Track, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
    - Indoor Track, 1976-1979, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Outdoor Track, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
    - Track, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Volleyball, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
    - Wrestling, 1975-1979, 1981, 5 folders (Box 13)
  - Sports schedules, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
  - Staff meeting minutes, 1978 Sept.-Nov. (Box 13)
  - Summer Camps, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - Surveys, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - Television Rights Information, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - Title IX, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Title IX report, 1976-1978 (Box 13)
  - Track and Field Committee, 1979 (Box 13)
  - University information, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - Steve Vacendek correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - Varsity Award letters, 1980-1983 (Box 13)
  - Volunteers for Youth, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
- Subject Files (UA86-7), 1977-1984, 2.5 boxes
  Accession contains material pertaining to Duke's football coaching vacancy in 1982; correspondence, memoranda, and minutes of the Athletic Council; subject correspondence including NCAA, Iron Dukes, and letters from students, staff, and alumni concerning the hiring of Steve Sloan as new head football coach; and material pertaining to various facility improvement projects.
  - Applicants, football coach, 1982 Nov.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Recommendations, Football Coach, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Athletic Council
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
    - Information, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Information, Butters, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Minutes, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 13)
  - ACC
    - Athletic Directors meeting, 1982 Sept. (Box 13)
    - Basketball Officials Clinic, 1982 Oct. (Box 13)
    - Butters correspondence, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Spring meeting, 1982 April-May (Box 13)
    - Television Committee meeting, 1982 June (Box 13)
  - Basketball applicants, 1980 March (Box 13)
  - College Football Association (CFA), 1981-1982
    - CFA Meeting, 1981 July-Aug. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence
    - Football (negative), 1982 Nov.-Dec. (Box 13)
    - Football (positive/general), 1982 Nov.-Dec. (Box 13)
    - Iron Dukes, 1980 Aug.-1982, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980 Sept.-1983 June, 4 folders (Box 13)
    - NCAA, 1981 Aug.-1982 Nov. (Box 13)
    - Northgreen Country Club, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - Jimmy Earle, College Basketball Officiating Service Agency, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - Facilities
    - Cameron, North Lobby renovations, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
    - Cameron, concourse, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Cameron, lights, 1983 (Box 13)